<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog - Henry Lim</title>
    <description>This is the first and only blog for Henry Lim. I will post some interesting story or some review to this blog. Just keep follow and subscribe to my blog.
</description>
    <link>http://limhenry.github.io/blog/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://limhenry.github.io/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2015 10:40:22 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2015 10:40:22 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Favorite Android Apps - Part 1</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I using Android phone, because it is nice and good. But not just the hardware make my Android phone nice but apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I am going to introduce some of my favorite apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;google-now-launcher&quot;&gt;Google Now Launcher&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google Now Launcher is developed by Google. It is useful if you are Google Now daily user (hourly?) because this launcher allow user to ‘swipe right to Google Now’. This allow me to access to Google Now even faster than ‘swipe up to Google Now’. This is definitely my favorite launcher. It’s fast and beautiful. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the way,the latest version of Google Now Launcher have the new Material Design (but no that awesome animation) for Android 4.1 - Android 4.4. Of course, Android 5.0/5.1 will include that animation (ripple effect?).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why I not using other launcher like Nova, Apex or stock launcher? This Google Now Launcher is the only launcher makes my phone looks like stock Android. I prefer clean design, and Google Now Launcher is what I need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;pb-app-box&quot; data-theme=&quot;discover&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://playboard.me/android/apps/com.google.android.launcher&quot;&gt;Google Now Launcher  (Playboard)&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.launcher&amp;amp;hl=en&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Google Now Launcher (Play Store)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot; src=&quot;//playboard.me/widgets/pb-app-box/1/pb_load_app_box.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;officesuite-8&quot;&gt;OfficeSuite 8&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This app is like a full Microsoft Office for your Android phone/tablet. It have almost all features you need. You can do everything in Office Suite 8. You can create and view .docx, .xlsx., .pptx, etc. files with this apps. You also can insert image into your document file (this is impossible to do it in &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.apps.docs.editors.docs&quot;&gt;Google Docs&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually, I using the Office Suite Pro 8 right now, so I can access to all their awesome features. Anyway, I didn’t brought it (not pirated thanks) but I get it FREE from Amazon App Store (sorry, that promotion ended long long time ago). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, no matter it’s free version of paid (pro) version, it’s still a powerful app. Er, of course, the paid version is still the best. Yes, it’s better than Google Docs/Slide/Sheet. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;pb-app-box&quot; data-theme=&quot;discover&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://playboard.me/android/apps/com.mobisystems.office&quot;&gt;OfficeSuite 8 + PDF Converter  (Playboard)&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.mobisystems.office&amp;amp;hl=en&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;OfficeSuite 8 + PDF Converter (Play Store)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot; src=&quot;//playboard.me/widgets/pb-app-box/1/pb_load_app_box.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;pb-app-box&quot; data-theme=&quot;discover&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://playboard.me/android/apps/com.mobisystems.editor.office_registered&quot;&gt;OfficeSuite 8 Pro + PDF  (Playboard)&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.mobisystems.editor.office_registered&amp;amp;hl=en&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;OfficeSuite 8 Pro + PDF (Play Store)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot; src=&quot;//playboard.me/widgets/pb-app-box/1/pb_load_app_box.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;heads-up-notifications&quot;&gt;Heads-up notifications&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You need this app if you are not running Android 5.0 (Lollipop users, you got this feature already, shh, don’t show off/hao-lian).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google introduced the new Notification design for Android 5.0, Lollipop. It’s nice and make your notification more visible, accessible, and configurable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, that’s only exclusive for Lollipop. Thanks to Heads-up notifications, those using Android 4.4 and below will also have the ability to enjoy this beautiful pop-up (heads-up) notification. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This app is highly customizable so you also can choose which app to show in heads-up notification or when notification will not show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conclusion: this app is totally free and download now! 
Note: it’s also open source and available in &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/SimenCodes/heads-up/&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;pb-app-box&quot; data-theme=&quot;discover&quot; data-lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://playboard.me/android/apps/codes.simen.l50notifications&quot;&gt;Heads-up notifications  (Playboard)&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=codes.simen.l50notifications&amp;amp;hl=en&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Heads-up notifications (Play Store)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot; src=&quot;//playboard.me/widgets/pb-app-box/1/pb_load_app_box.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, three apps should enough. I will talk the other apps next time (Part 2 is coming soon). Anyway, remember to &lt;a href=&quot;http://eepurl.com/bdrwRz&quot;&gt;SUBSCRIBE&lt;/a&gt; to my newsletter in order to get the latest alert/notification when new post in updated. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any questions/comments? You are welcome to comment at the Discussion area below. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bye bye and have a nice day. 
* Chinese New Year is coming ^^&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: if got any funny grammar errors, don’t laugh but &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#110;&amp;#114;&amp;#121;&amp;#108;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#046;&amp;#101;&amp;#118;&amp;#101;&amp;#114;&amp;#121;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#103;&amp;#064;&amp;#103;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&amp;#063;&amp;#115;&amp;#117;&amp;#098;&amp;#106;&amp;#101;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#061;&amp;#070;&amp;#117;&amp;#110;&amp;#110;&amp;#121;&amp;#032;&amp;#071;&amp;#114;&amp;#097;&amp;#109;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#114;&quot;&gt;email&lt;/a&gt; me, thanks ^^.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2015 20:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/02/08/My-Favorite-Android-Apps-Part1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/02/08/My-Favorite-Android-Apps-Part1.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>[UPDATE, IT’S REAL] Android 5.1</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Few hours ago, Google updated their site for Android One in Indonesia with Android 5.1. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now, it’s real and confirmed. Android 5.1 is now running on Evercoss One X, Mito Impact and Nexian Journey. And it will also available to update for Nexus 5,6 and 9 very very soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is some images from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.androidpolice.com/2015/02/04/the-next-android-revision-is-indeed-android-5-1-lollipop-already-shipping-on-android-one-phones-coming-soon-to-nexus-devices/&quot;&gt;AndroidPolice.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.androidpolice.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/nexus2cee_wm_android-5.1-lollipop.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;AP&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.androidpolice.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/nexus2cee_wm_2015-02-04-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;AP&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.androidpolice.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/nexus2cee_wm_2015-02-04-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;AP&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We mentioned this few hours ago:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Android One is coming to Indonesia very very soon and the phone will running the ‘latest’ version of Android 5.1. What? 5.1??? YES, 5.1 not 5.01!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/Paz7t9i.png&quot; alt=&quot;Imgur&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;h2 id=&quot;android-51&quot;&gt;Android 5.1&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The sweetest version of Android, 5.0 Lollipop is announced during Google I/O 2014. And now Google ‘introduce’ the new Android 5.1 indirectly but it sound legit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Source : &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.android.com/intl/en-GB_id/one/&quot;&gt;Android.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: if got any funny grammar errors, don’t laugh but &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#110;&amp;#114;&amp;#121;&amp;#108;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#046;&amp;#101;&amp;#118;&amp;#101;&amp;#114;&amp;#121;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#103;&amp;#064;&amp;#103;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&amp;#063;&amp;#115;&amp;#117;&amp;#098;&amp;#106;&amp;#101;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#061;&amp;#070;&amp;#117;&amp;#110;&amp;#110;&amp;#121;&amp;#032;&amp;#071;&amp;#114;&amp;#097;&amp;#109;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#114;&quot;&gt;email&lt;/a&gt; me, thanks ^^.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 02:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/02/05/Android-5.1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/02/05/Android-5.1.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Windows 10 Review</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft announced the latest build of Windows 10 Technical Preview Build 9926 on 23 January 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Windows 10. Pricing? Free, seriously. Windows 10 will available to upgrade for every Windows 7, 8 and 8.1 users. FREE. No hidden charge. Just you are not running a pirated version of Windows, LOL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, any new things/features in this latest build of Windows 10?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hey-cortana&quot;&gt;Hey Cortana.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, CORTANA. People love technology. People love artificial intelligence (AI). We got Siri for iOS users, Google Now for Android (and iOS, oops) and Cortana for Windows phone. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, the biggest problem is: computer should smarter than smartphone, every features in smartphone should also available in Computer. So, Microsoft introduce Cortana, a Microsoft AI for Windows 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is that awesome? Currently, no. Maybe it’s still under development/beta. Anyway, how is the quality/performance/feature of Cortana in this latest build of Windows 10? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The available features is still very limited. You only can set reminder, ask for weather, and I think that’s all. You can’t ask her (Cortana is a female…) “who is Obama?”. If you ask her, she will simply redirect you to Bing.com (Where is my Google?)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, Cortana in Windows 10, let’s ignore this feature until the next build or the final release of Windows. Hope Cortana can become better and awesome future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hello-start-menu&quot;&gt;Hello Start Menu.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, Start Menu is back! But don’t so happy. The ‘new’ start menu is something like the combination of Windows 7’s start menu and Windows 8’s metro start. It looks weird and I don’t like it. I still prefer Windows 8 metro start or Windows 7 start menu. Just don’t combine together. Anyway, it should work better in touch screen mode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;virtual-desktop&quot;&gt;Virtual Desktop&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Virtual Desktop. This is one of the features in Mac OS long long time ago. And finally available in Windows (without any third-party add-ons). It works quite nice but it’s a little bit unfamiliar to Windows user. It’s still a nice feature anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-windows-pc-just-only-usd-35&quot;&gt;A Windows PC just only USD 35?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wait wait. Did Microsoft said Windows 10 is a OS for any devices from no screen to phone, tablet, laptop, PC, even TV? Yes. Windows 10 is bigger and stronger than you think. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Windows PC just 35USD? Seriously, Windows JUST announced Windows 10 is also available for Raspberry Pi 2 for free. Our next generation, 35USD computer is coming soon. More info: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.raspberrypi.org/raspberry-pi-2-on-sale/&quot;&gt;raspberrypi.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Windows 10 is nice. But I will continue using my beautiful and fast Ubuntu i mentioned few days ago. &lt;a href=&quot;http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/01/30/Quick-review-of-My-PC.html&quot;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading my blog and support me, have a nice day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/XGte9Y7.png&quot; alt=&quot;Imgur&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/Aq8f9dk.png&quot; alt=&quot;Imgur&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/ZpPqiTf.png&quot; alt=&quot;Imgur&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/MNISvh0.png&quot; alt=&quot;Imgur&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/ReJCwO3.png&quot; alt=&quot;Imgur&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/hNUwPTU.png&quot; alt=&quot;Imgur&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: if got any funny grammar errors, don’t laugh but &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#110;&amp;#114;&amp;#121;&amp;#108;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#046;&amp;#101;&amp;#118;&amp;#101;&amp;#114;&amp;#121;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#103;&amp;#064;&amp;#103;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&amp;#063;&amp;#115;&amp;#117;&amp;#098;&amp;#106;&amp;#101;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#061;&amp;#070;&amp;#117;&amp;#110;&amp;#110;&amp;#121;&amp;#032;&amp;#071;&amp;#114;&amp;#097;&amp;#109;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#114;&quot;&gt;email&lt;/a&gt; me, thanks ^^.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 20:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/02/04/Windows-10-Review.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/02/04/Windows-10-Review.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Xperia M2 Review</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Sony Xperia M2, the phone I am using right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sony introduced this mid-range phone, Xperia M2 in CES 2014 and released in Q2 ‘14.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The price range is around USD300 (it’s around MYR 799 due today).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not cheap, and I strongly NOT RECOMMENDING you if you wanna to buy a new Android phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why? It’s that not good? No, it’s nice, but please don’t buy an old phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, let’s talk about this phone. Design, it’s nice. It has the (nearly) same design with Sony flagship devices like Z3, Z2 and Z1. But it is not using glass but plastic. That plastic is like a fingerprint-magnet, just holding that phone for a few seconds without cover, the back of phone will be full of fingerprint. So, a phone cover is highly recommended if you are using Xperia M2 right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Performance, it’s like a normal mid-range Android smartphone, it’s not so slow, normal browsing, Facebook, all no problem. Games? It still can run “Asphalt 8: Airborne” without any lag (the loading speed might be a bit bit longer ( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°) ).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Camera. Firmware problem and it’s solved. Xperia M2 released to public with Android 4.3, Jelly Bean. During that time, the quality of camera is a bit horrible, especially the image noise. Luckily the problem solved after the Kitkat update. By the way, it’s running with a 8MP camera, with Full HD support. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Front camera of Xperia M2? I just ignore that camera. The front camera is ‘unusable’. A VGA-front camera, that’s is totally horrible. If you are a selfie-lover, just simply don’t buy this phone. Brought already, use the rear camera. Thanks to the Camera button, you still can take selfie with that rear-camera, just need a little practise and skill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaker. It’s quite loud, thanks to Sony’s xLOUD technology and ClearPhase. You can enjoy a ‘not bad’ quality with Xperia M2. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BUT….  my phone having the biggest problem in this world (it look like I am the only one having this problem), which is the sound output (speaker and earphone, but no problem with Bluetooth earphone/speaker). The sound will stop playing randomly for 5 seconds -1 minute when the screen is off. I have no way to solve it, even after asking in XDA and Sony Support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conclusion: DON’T BUY.it’s not so cheap anyway. Buy Nexus 5 instead. Nexus 5 is a great phone but costs you around MYR 1200. Want cheaper, buy Moto G (second gen if possible)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: there is still no news about Android 5.0, Lollipop official update for Xperia M2. Sad news T.T&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Hgm7sPbXeVk&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: if got any funny grammar errors, don’t laugh but &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#110;&amp;#114;&amp;#121;&amp;#108;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#046;&amp;#101;&amp;#118;&amp;#101;&amp;#114;&amp;#121;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#103;&amp;#064;&amp;#103;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&amp;#063;&amp;#115;&amp;#117;&amp;#098;&amp;#106;&amp;#101;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#061;&amp;#070;&amp;#117;&amp;#110;&amp;#110;&amp;#121;&amp;#032;&amp;#071;&amp;#114;&amp;#097;&amp;#109;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#114;&quot;&gt;email&lt;/a&gt; me, thanks ^^.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 20:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/02/03/Sony-Xperia-M2-Review.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/02/03/Sony-Xperia-M2-Review.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Google Glass, Hands On and a very quick review</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Google Glass, Google Glass, Google Glass, Google Glass, Google Glass, Google Glass, Google Glass, Google Glass…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It became my favourite tech gadget the moment it announced to public.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I managed to borrow that awesome Google Glass from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wenjiun.my/&quot;&gt;Yap Wen Jiun&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google Glass is awesome, it’s light and it’s amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You probably know how it works and how it look like. But it is hard to know the feeling when you are wearing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, I got the chance to borrow it after the MMU Android Meetup in 31 October 2014. I was so excited when that Google Glass is really in front of me. I took out my glasses, and put the Google Glass on my face. Something happens! I saw a blur screen in front of me. Kay, I immediately knew the reason and finally, I ‘force’ to wear double glasses (my perspective glasses + Google Glass).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Double glasses on my face. It’s weird. But whatever, just ignore it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The speaker of Google Glass. It’s awesome. It uses the Bone Conduction Transducer (BCT), so the sound is pretty amazing, it’s loud and crystal clear. Microphone? Awesome. I was using that Google Glass in a hall (quite noisy there), but Google Glass was still listening to what I am talking about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Screen? Amazing. The HUD makes you like Iron Man, a small rectangle screen floating in front of you (it is around 2-3m in front of you). And it’s ‘floating’. That is quite a weird experience. And it’s also looks semi-transparent, so the screen will not bother you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok Glass, take a picture. Ok Glass, record a video. Ok Glass, Google, what is Google Glass? I was so busy with trying that piece of technology. That is the real technology. The future is here. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google Glass is expensive. It costs you USD1500 or it’s around MYR5000. IT IS VERY VERY EXPENSIVE! I am just waiting for one day (and I believe it’s coming), a cheaper version of Google Glass is going to release to the consumer, or maybe less than USD300? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s coming soon to us because &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.google.com/111626127367496192147/posts/9uiwXY42tvc&quot;&gt;“Google Glass is graduating from Google[x] labs” &lt;/a&gt;. I hope Google Glass Consumer Edition will announce during Google I/O this year, maybe?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hello Glass, Hello Google, Hello World.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/W793fXo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Imgur&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/UoqkTtw.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Imgur&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/xxlsjlz.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Imgur&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/SV8V5Lf.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Imgur&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: if got any funny grammar errors, don’t laugh but &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#110;&amp;#114;&amp;#121;&amp;#108;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#046;&amp;#101;&amp;#118;&amp;#101;&amp;#114;&amp;#121;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#103;&amp;#064;&amp;#103;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&amp;#063;&amp;#115;&amp;#117;&amp;#098;&amp;#106;&amp;#101;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#061;&amp;#070;&amp;#117;&amp;#110;&amp;#110;&amp;#121;&amp;#032;&amp;#071;&amp;#114;&amp;#097;&amp;#109;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#114;&quot;&gt;email&lt;/a&gt; me, thanks ^^.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 22:20:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/01/31/Google-Glass-Hands-On-And-Review.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/01/31/Google-Glass-Hands-On-And-Review.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quick review of my PC (Ubuntu)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A quick review of my PC with Ubuntu&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am using ASUS X550LD right now, overall it is OK. This computer is pre-installed with Windows 8.1 but…… (Most of the time) I am using Ubuntu 14.04.1. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why? Is Ubuntu better than Windows?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The answer is yes and no. I can’t afford to buy a MacBook, so I ‘force’ to buy a Windows PC. And now, I installed this Ubuntu to my lappy. Firstly, it runs sucks because the graphic card (NVIDIA Geforce 820M) can’t detect, until one day (I also dunno the reason) my Ubuntu detected that graphic card without any reason. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, now graphic card is detected, it is time to say goodbye to Windows. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, Ubuntu is an OS like Mac OS, but you “can’t run Photoshop”. It’s fast, just I hate that default design. Thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/HiiYL&quot;&gt;Hii&lt;/a&gt;, he introduced and taught me something very awesome which is called “Gnome”. It’s awesome and beautiful. Somehow I love &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.google.com/design/spec/material-design/introduction.html&quot;&gt;Material Design&lt;/a&gt; so much, so I decided to make my Ubuntu more material design. In conclusion, it’s very very nice!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Performance? Yes, it is better than Windows. For example, it’s easier to run Jekyll in Ubuntu compare to Windows. Another example is: Android Studio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last time, I didn’t know Ubuntu is so fast, then I using Windows to develop and build some Android app. It’s suck, slow and you will see “Not Responding” almost everyday (every hour, maybe?). The compile app duration in Windows is around 3-4 minutes (in my case), but when I compile in Ubuntu, it only took 30-40 seconds. Seriously? Yep, Ubuntu is amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing (two actually), make my Ubuntu a bit ‘haiz’ are speaker and touchpad. Due to kernel/driver problem, that touchpad doesn’t work with my laptop, luckily I got mouse. Next, speaker. The sound in Ubuntu is really very ‘unlistenable’. Luckily I got &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.webupd8.org/2013/03/install-pulseaudio-with-built-in-system.html&quot;&gt;Pulse Audio Equalizer&lt;/a&gt;, which make my laptop’s speaker better a little bit, but not so nice. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How about the Microsoft latest OS, Windows 10, which is still under technical preview, it’s still very buggy. For me, Windows 7, 8, 8.1 and 10 are same. But what I need is a fast OS, so Hello Ubuntu, Hello Linux, Hello World.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will talk about my opinion and hand-on with Windows 10 Technical Preview in next post. Thanks for reading my post, have a nice day. ^^&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scereenshot:
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/ubCiK7d.png&quot; alt=&quot;Desktop&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/taVGc9q.png&quot; alt=&quot;Taskbar&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/hJh5gtG.png&quot; alt=&quot;Setting&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/JVZmfQy.png&quot; alt=&quot;Task Manager&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/7iaafQq.png&quot; alt=&quot;App&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/txYvGGz.png&quot; alt=&quot;File Manager&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/E5ddFzw.png&quot; alt=&quot;Spotify&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: if got any funny grammar errors, don’t laugh but &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#110;&amp;#114;&amp;#121;&amp;#108;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#046;&amp;#101;&amp;#118;&amp;#101;&amp;#114;&amp;#121;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#103;&amp;#064;&amp;#103;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&amp;#063;&amp;#115;&amp;#117;&amp;#098;&amp;#106;&amp;#101;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#061;&amp;#070;&amp;#117;&amp;#110;&amp;#110;&amp;#121;&amp;#032;&amp;#071;&amp;#114;&amp;#097;&amp;#109;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#114;&quot;&gt;email&lt;/a&gt; me, thanks ^^.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 05:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/01/31/Quick-review-of-My-PC.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/01/31/Quick-review-of-My-PC.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My First Post</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello World.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am Henry Lim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a student, developer and human of course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this is my first blog and it’s hosted on GitHub. Anyway, this awesome blog is built by using &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;. It’s quite simple to build a blog like this. At the meantime, this blog is still under development and the blog (layout) will update from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometime, you might ask me, why don’t use blogger or wordpress. In Blogger/WordPress, you just write your post, and you can straight away post it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But in GitHub, you need to create a blog by yourself (thanks to Jekyll, that save my life…). Then, you can change the layout by using CSS without any limitation (which is nearly impossible in Blogger/WordPress), and I got a very lousy reason to learn HTML/CSS ( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°), LOL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love web, so I love HTML. Of course, I only love a beautiful website, maybe Material Design?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since this blog is still under development, it’s time to let me continue to make this website better and nicer, &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading my first post on this website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the way, remember to visit my home page : &lt;a href=&quot;http://limhenry.github.io&quot;&gt;limhenry.github.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a nice day ^^&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 02:17:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/01/31/My-First-Post.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/01/31/My-First-Post.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
