<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog - Henry Lim</title>
    <description>This is the first and only blog for Henry Lim. I will post some interesting story or some review to this blog. Just keep follow to my blog.
</description>
    <link>http://limhenry.github.io/blog/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://limhenry.github.io/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 16:53:34 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 16:53:34 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Google Glass, Hands On and a very quick review</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Finally, I managed to borrow Google Glass from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wenjiun.my/&quot;&gt;Yap Wen Jiun&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google Glass is awesome, it’s light and it’s amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You probably know how it works and how it look like. But it is hard to know the feeling when you are wearing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, I got the chance to borrow it after the MMU Android Meetup in 31 October 2014. I was so excited when that Google Glass is really in front of me. I took out my glasses, and put the Google Glass on my face. Something happens! I saw a blur screen in front of me. Kay, I immediately knew the reason and finally, I ‘force’ to wear double glasses (my perspective glasses + Google Glass).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Double glasses on my face. It’s weird. But whatever, just ignore it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The speaker of Google Glass. It’s awesome. It uses the Bone Conduction Transducer (BCT), so the sound is pretty amazing, it’s loud and crystal clear. Microphone? Awesome. I was using that Google Glass in a hall (quite noisy there), but Google Glass was still listening to what I am talking about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Screen? Amazing. The HUD makes you like Iron Man, a small rectangle screen floating in front of you (it is around 2-3m in front of you). And it’s ‘floating’. That is quite a weird experience. And it’s also looks semi-transparent, so the screen will not bother you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok Glass, take a picture. Ok Glass, record a video. Ok Glass, Google, what is Google Glass? I was so busy with trying that piece of technology. That is the real technology. The future is here. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google Glass is expensive. It costs you USD1500 or it’s around MYR5000. IT IS VERY VERY EXPENSIVE! I am just waiting for one day (and I believe it’s coming), a cheaper version of Google Glass is going to release to the consumer, or maybe less than USD300? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s coming soon to us because &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.google.com/111626127367496192147/posts/9uiwXY42tvc&quot;&gt;“Google Glass is graduating from Google[x] labs” &lt;/a&gt;. I hope Google Glass Consumer Edition will announce during Google I/O this year, maybe?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hello Glass, Hello Google, Hello World.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/W793fXo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Imgur&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/UoqkTtw.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Imgur&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/xxlsjlz.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Imgur&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/SV8V5Lf.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Imgur&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: if got any funny grammar errors, don’t laugh but &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#110;&amp;#114;&amp;#121;&amp;#108;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#046;&amp;#101;&amp;#118;&amp;#101;&amp;#114;&amp;#121;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#103;&amp;#064;&amp;#103;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&amp;#063;&amp;#115;&amp;#117;&amp;#098;&amp;#106;&amp;#101;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#061;&amp;#070;&amp;#117;&amp;#110;&amp;#110;&amp;#121;&amp;#032;&amp;#071;&amp;#114;&amp;#097;&amp;#109;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#114;&quot;&gt;email&lt;/a&gt; me, thanks ^^.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 22:20:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/01/31/Google-Glass-Hands-On-And-Review.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/01/31/Google-Glass-Hands-On-And-Review.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quick review of my PC (Ubuntu)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A quick review of my PC with Ubuntu&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am using ASUS X550LD right now, overall it is OK. This computer is pre-installed with Windows 8.1 but…… (Most of the time) I am using Ubuntu 14.04.1. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why? Is Ubuntu better than Windows?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The answer is yes and no. I can’t afford to buy a MacBook, so I ‘force’ to buy a Windows PC. And now, I installed this Ubuntu to my lappy. Firstly, it runs sucks because the graphic card (NVIDIA Geforce 820M) can’t detect, until one day (I also dunno the reason) my Ubuntu detected that graphic card without any reason. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, now graphic card is detected, it is time to say goodbye to Windows. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, Ubuntu is an OS like Mac OS, but you “can’t run Photoshop”. It’s fast, just I hate that default design. Thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/HiiYL&quot;&gt;Hii&lt;/a&gt;, he introduced and taught me something very awesome which is called “Gnome”. It’s awesome and beautiful. Somehow I love &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.google.com/design/spec/material-design/introduction.html&quot;&gt;Material Design&lt;/a&gt; so much, so I decided to make my Ubuntu more material design. In conclusion, it’s very very nice!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Performance? Yes, it is better than Windows. For example, it’s easier to run Jekyll in Ubuntu compare to Windows. Another example is: Android Studio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last time, I didn’t know Ubuntu is so fast, then I using Windows to develop and build some Android app. It’s suck, slow and you will see “Not Responding” almost everyday (every hour, maybe?). The compile app duration in Windows is around 3-4 minutes (in my case), but when I compile in Ubuntu, it only took 30-40 seconds. Seriously? Yep, Ubuntu is amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing (two actually), make my Ubuntu a bit ‘haiz’ are speaker and touchpad. Due to kernel/driver problem, that touchpad doesn’t work with my laptop, luckily I got mouse. Next, speaker. The sound in Ubuntu is really very ‘unlistenable’. Luckily I got &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.webupd8.org/2013/03/install-pulseaudio-with-built-in-system.html&quot;&gt;Pulse Audio Equalizer&lt;/a&gt;, which make my laptop’s speaker better a little bit, but not so nice. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How about the Microsoft latest OS, Windows 10, which is still under technical preview, it’s still very buggy. For me, Windows 7, 8, 8.1 and 10 are same. But what I need is a fast OS, so Hello Ubuntu, Hello Linux, Hello World.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will talk about my opinion and hand-on with Windows 10 Technical Preview in next post. Thanks for reading my post, have a nice day. ^^&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scereenshot:
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/ubCiK7d.png&quot; alt=&quot;Desktop&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/taVGc9q.png&quot; alt=&quot;Taskbar&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/hJh5gtG.png&quot; alt=&quot;Setting&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/JVZmfQy.png&quot; alt=&quot;Task Manager&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/7iaafQq.png&quot; alt=&quot;App&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/txYvGGz.png&quot; alt=&quot;File Manager&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/E5ddFzw.png&quot; alt=&quot;Spotify&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: if got any funny grammar errors, don’t laugh but &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#104;&amp;#101;&amp;#110;&amp;#114;&amp;#121;&amp;#108;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#046;&amp;#101;&amp;#118;&amp;#101;&amp;#114;&amp;#121;&amp;#116;&amp;#104;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#103;&amp;#064;&amp;#103;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&amp;#063;&amp;#115;&amp;#117;&amp;#098;&amp;#106;&amp;#101;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#061;&amp;#070;&amp;#117;&amp;#110;&amp;#110;&amp;#121;&amp;#032;&amp;#071;&amp;#114;&amp;#097;&amp;#109;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#114;&quot;&gt;email&lt;/a&gt; me, thanks ^^.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 05:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/01/31/Quick-review-of-My-PC.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/01/31/Quick-review-of-My-PC.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My First Post</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello World.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am Henry Lim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a student, developer and human of course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this is my first blog and it’s hosted on GitHub. Anyway, this awesome blog is built by using &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;. It’s quite simple to build a blog like this. At the meantime, this blog is still under development and the blog (layout) will update from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometime, you might ask me, why don’t use blogger or wordpress. In Blogger/WordPress, you just write your post, and you can straight away post it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But in GitHub, you need to create a blog by yourself (thanks to Jekyll, that save my life…). Then, you can change the layout by using CSS without any limitation (which is nearly impossible in Blogger/WordPress), and I got a very lousy reason to learn HTML/CSS ( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°), LOL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love web, so I love HTML. Of course, I only love a beautiful website, maybe Material Design?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since this blog is still under development, it’s time to let me continue to make this website better and nicer, &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading my first post on this website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the way, remember to visit my home page : &lt;a href=&quot;http://limhenry.github.io&quot;&gt;limhenry.github.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a nice day ^^&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 02:17:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/01/31/My-First-Post.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://limhenry.github.io/blog/2015/01/31/My-First-Post.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
